artsuae.com 2010-11-13

# Privacy Statement - Spiky Penguin

**Introduction**  
Nothing is more important to us than protecting the privacy of our clients. This Privacy Policy tells you how we collect information from you, what we disclose, how we use it and otherwise maintain such information. By providing personal information to Spiky Penguin via the Website or otherwise, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as set out below.

**Application**  
In this Privacy Policy, we refer to the Spiky Penguin website as the "Website". Use of the Website is subject to Spiky Penguin's Terms of Service. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into the Website Terms of Service, and should therefore be read with the Terms of Service to fully understand your rights and obligations and the rights and obligations of Spiky Penguin.

**Acceptance of terms**  
BY USING THE WEBSITE OR BY OTHERWISE PROVIDING SPIKY PENGUIN YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO BE BOUND BY THE PRIVACY POLICY, DO NOT PROVIDE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION TO SPIKY PENGUIN WHETHER VIA THE WEBSITE OR OTHERWISE. 

IF YOU DO NOT ACCEPT THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE TERMS OF SERVICE, PLEASE IMMEDIATELY DISCONTINUE USING THIS WEBSITE AND, AS STATED ABOVE, DO NOT PROVIDE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION TO SPIKY PENGUIN. 

**Information collected about you**  
Spiky Penguin collects personal information through a variety of methods, including via the Website, over the phone, direct mail or otherwise. In all instances, however, such collection shall be completely voluntary and at your discretion. It is always your choice whether or not to provide Spiky Penguin your personal information. 

There are four types of information that Spiky Penguin collects about you: 

A. Personal Registration Information We collect the contact information you supply when you register or sign up for one of Spiky Penguin's services, including your name, address, phone, fax or e-mail address and the password you select. This information, which we refer to as "Personal Registration Information", may be edited by you at any time, either using your password or contacting a Spiky Penguin customer representative at [customerservice@spikypenguin.com](mailto:customerservice@spikypenguin.com). If you do not wish to modify your personal information over the Internet, you may contact one of our customer service representatives at the number listed at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. 

B. Limited Access Information We collect information such as nature of your profession, duration you've been in the profession, personal preferences. We use this information to be able to provide you with better, more enhanced services. Specifically, we use this additional information with our proprietary search software with the goal of increasing the opportunities to match your profile with others. This information, which we refer to as Limited Access Information, is accessible only to you and the people who you give permission to access your files. 

C. Publicly Posted Information We collect the information you post or want to be publicly viewable, such as your online portfolio on Spiky Penguin. We refer to this information as Publicly Posted Information, and it is accessible by anyone with Internet access. 

D. Cookies and Tracking Information Spiky Penguin uses "cookies" to personalize your experience on our Website. Cookies are small data files that contain information about you, that are stored on your hard drive when you visit certain websites. Many popular websites use cookies to store your preferences on a particular site. Cookies collect information such as your browser type, time and length of your visit. Our use of your personal information largely depends on the use of cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. Note that if you refuse cookies, you may be unable to use certain services in the Website.

**Use of personal information; right to opt out**  
Your personal information will be used only to, among other reasons, provide you the services you have requested, improve the content on our Website, help us serve your needs and requests better, and generally support your use of the Website. Without limiting the foregoing, personal information collected on the Website or through other voluntary means may be used by Spiky Penguin, in following ways:  
    to specify unique preferences and to provide personalized content;  
    to track user trends and patterns;  
    expand our online directories or contact you regarding future Spiky Penguin and third party products and services;  
    to communicate special offers and featured items to you including notices pertaining to future Spiky Penguin and third party products and services;  
    to respond to your customer service inquires or requests;  
    provide you with certain information about products or services, from us or third parties, we think may interest you.  
    to inform you of upcoming events, promotions, and developments with respect to membership information, including changes to our Service Fees; and  
    to enhance website operation and efficiency.  
Spiky Penguin will not sell or otherwise transfer your personal information to unaffiliated third parties other than in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not want the information you provide to Spiky Penguin used in the above noted manner, you can indicate this preference to our customer service representatives at [customerservice@spikypenguin.com](mailto:customerservice@spikypenguin.com) or by calling our customer service number which is noted at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. Please note, however, depending on what you wish to opt-out from, may impact on our ability to provide you the services you are requesting. 

Spiky Penguin reserves the right to provide aggregate data to third parties for statistical analysis. Such data will not be linked to any particular individuals. In addition, we also reserve the right to disclose your personal information if such disclosure is made pursuant to a legal proceeding or is required by law. 

We will only keep your personal information for as long as it remains necessary or relevant for the purposes stated above or as otherwise required by law.

**Advertisers on Spiky Penguin**  
From time to time, we conduct statistical analyses of the collective behavior and characteristics of our users to measure interest in and use of Spiky Penguin's services. We sometimes provide our advertisers with this statistical information, such as the number of users that have been exposed to or clicked on their advertising banners. However, we only provide aggregated data from these analyses to third parties, we do not provide personal data characteristics such as your name, address or phone number or any other information, which can identify you as an individual. 

Spiky Penguin permits third parties to offer their services to visitors of our Website through advertisements. Spiky Penguin is not responsible for the actions or policies of our advertisers or other third parties; therefore, we recommend that you verify the applicable privacy practices of any other website or third party before you provide them with your personal information. 

Outside companies advertise on Spiky Penguin using banner advertisements. When you click on these ads to visit an advertiser's website, you may be given a cookie. While we use cookies in other parts of our Website (this use is described in more detail above), only the companies advertising on our Website collect the cookies you may receive with the banner ads. We do not have access to or control over our advertisers' cookies or data collection practices.

**Security**  
Your Personal Registration Information -- the information you supply when you register or sign up for one of Spiky Penguin's services -- is password-protected so that only you and Spiky Penguin have access to this information. Your Limited Access Information is accessible only to you and the people who you give permission to access your files. Your Publicly Posted Information is available to anyone with Internet access. Your Cookie and Tracking Information is used by us for internal purposes only to provide you with personalized service. 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100 percent secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Spiky Penguin cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us through our Website or that you download from our online products or services on our Website, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems. Your personal information resides on a secure server that only authorized Spiky Penguin personnel and contractors have access to via password. 

Please note that there are several places on the Website where you can transmit credit card information in order to complete a purchase transaction. We have taken steps to ensure that credit card and other financial information remains well protected. Any time we ask for a credit card number, we transmit that credit card number in an encrypted format. We use industry-standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption.

**Changing personal information**  
At your request, Spiky Penguin will provide you with access to the personal information we may have on file about you and to allow you to update and/or correct personal information to the extent such information is inaccurate. 

To notify us of changes to your personal information, to request that information about you is deleted or deactivated from our records, or to withdraw your consent for the collection and/or use of your personal information please e-mail us at [customerservice@spikypenguin.com](mailto:customerservice@spikypenguin.com) or call us at the customer service number located at the bottom of this Privacy Policy.

**Modification to the privacy policy**  
Spiky Penguin reserves the right to make changes, modifications, additions or deletions to this Privacy Policy at any time. Spiky Penguin will make reasonable efforts to notify you of such modifications by email to the address listed by the registered user, posting a notice that modifications have been made on the top or this page or on Spiky Penguin home page, or other means that Spiky Penguin believes is reasonable in the circumstances. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to maintain a valid e-mail address as a registered user and to review this Privacy Policy periodically to be aware of any modifications. Your continued use of Spiky Penguin after such modifications constitutes your acknowledgement of the modified Privacy Policy, and agreement to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

**How to contact Spiky Penguin**  
If you have any questions, comments, concerns or require more information about this Privacy Policy or the personal information practices of Spiky Penguin, please direct your inquiry to the attention of our customer service department at:   
Spiky Penguin  
00971553539253
